winsms.co.za 2013-03-19

# WinSMS Privacy Policy

At WinSMS we respect and take steps to protect your privacy. We strive to make our site a safe environment for everyone who visits and uses WinSMS services. We are committed to providing you the best possible online service and experience as well as the best products and services. The purpose of this policy statement is to address any security concerns you may have.

## How We Use Information collected

We use information that you provide us to keep track of the WinSMS services you have signed up to receive and or use. We may also use personally identifiable information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyse site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our site's content and layout. We do this in an attempt to improve our site and better tailor it to meet our users' needs. We may also use personally identifiable information about you to deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests, such as targeted banners and promotions. We use your email address and cell number to contact you regarding administrative notices or latest news from time to time. We use information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the site, to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms and Conditions. 

## Protection of Database Information

Any information sent to WinSMS for messaging and or storage purposes will remain the property of the account holder. WinSMS will at no time collect or redistribute this information without your consent, except where legally required by law to do so. This is with particular reference to any database, numbers and/or recipient details that you may deliver to us, or store on our databases. 

## Disclosure of Your Information

We do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party. We must however comply with court orders, information requests from government agencies and regulators and other legal and regulatory processes that may require the disclosure of your personally identifiable information.

##  Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.  This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on WinSMS.co.za to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.  This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

## Questions and comments

We're always happy to answer your questions and listen to your comments.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy or its implementation, please contact us.

Acceptance of this privacy policy is a condition to your use of our services and you agree to be bound by all of its terms and conditions.

Please also carefully read the WinSMS Terms and Conditions.
